<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 15:13:37 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kalimpong Sightseeing</title>
      <link>http://example.org/sightseeing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 15:13:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/sightseeing/</guid>
      <description>Deolo Hill  This is the major attraction in East Kalimpong. The tourism department has created an 8-acre lush parkland with manicured flower gardens and several view points with breathtaking views of Kanchenjunga, Durpin hill, Kalimpong Township and the valley with rivers flowing through them. Deolo hill is the highest point of Kalimpong with an altitude of about 5,500ft. There is a GTA (erstwhile DGHC) lodge here and a multi cuisine restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rooms &amp; Suites</title>
      <link>http://example.org/rooms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 15:13:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/rooms/</guid>
      <description>Deluxe Room  Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.    Deluxe Room with View  Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Package Tours</title>
      <link>http://example.org/packagetours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 15:13:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/packagetours/</guid>
      <description>Lava &amp; Loleygaon Trip  Drive to Loleygaon (2.5hours), take a canopy walk amongst tree tops on a thrilling tree-top hanging bridge made in lush jungle, then drive to Lava (1hour), visit the Lava monastery and drive back in the evening via Algarah. If you plan to stay overnight in Lava or Loleygaon, know what else you can do &amp; where to stay.    Pedong and View Points  Take a short drive of about half an hour and see the ruins of Damsang Fort of 1690.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>http://example.org/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 15:13:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/gallery/</guid>
      <description> View all   Temple   Resort   Park   Nursery  Others                       </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>http://example.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 15:13:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/contact/</guid>
      <description>Address: Shreeniketan Lodge   Dr. B L Dixit Road, Kalimpong - 734301, West Bengal.  Tel: +91-95470-12255   Fax: +91-94752-33421   Email: shreeniketanlodge@gmail.com       Message Form  Name:  Email:  Subject:  Message:     Thank you. We have received your message and will contact you back shortly.  Something went wrong. Please contact us via email or phone. We truly apologize for the inconvenience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Shreeniketan</title>
      <link>http://example.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 15:12:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/about/</guid>
      <description>The most vivid travel experiences usually find you by accident, and the qualities that will make you fall in love with a place are rarely the features that took you there, but the essence itself…..Paradise found….. Tucked away in the foothills of the Himalays this heaven could well be described as the Garden of Eden.
Shreeniketan Lodge is an ideal place to enjoy a peaceful vacation in Kalimpong. You’ll wake up to the singing of birds every morning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>